Hello friends, today ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company Limited has
published its quarter three results and if you look here,
all the parameters are
showing in red on quarter wise basis, that is, on quarter
wise basis, the revenue and
profit of the company has decreased but on year on year basis, there has been
growth in it. So now let's talk in detail
about the company's numbers and
first of all check the revenue of the company.
In this quarter, the revenue of the company has come to
4559 crores, whereas in the previous quarter it was 4669
crores and in the December 21 quarter of last year, the
company had 47 crores. If we
look here, on quarter wise basis, the
revenue of the company has decreased by 2%, but on year on year basis, there has been a
growth of 14%. If we
talk about operating profit, then
in this order, the company's operating profit has come to 454
crores, whereas in the previous quarter it was 574
crores and in the December 20 quarter of last year, the
operating profit of the company was 409
crores. If we look here, there has been a huge
decline of 21% in the
operating profit of the company.  If we look at the profit on a quarterly basis
and on air and airways, then it is
necessary that there has been an increase of 11%. After this, if we talk about the
operating profit margin of the company,
then in this quadrant the company has an operating
margin of 10%, whereas in the previous quarter it
was 12% and in the December 2021 quarter of the last year, the
operating profit
margin of the company was 10%. If we look here, then on a
quarterly basis, the operating
profit margin of the company has decreased by 2% points,
but on an air-on-air basis, it has increased.
Apart from this, if we talk about the net profit of the company, then
in this quarter the net profit of the company
is Rs 30053 crore, whereas
in the previous quarter it was Rs 591 crore and
in the December 21 quarter of the last year, the
network of the company was Rs 328 crore. If we look here, then the
net profit of the company has decreased by 40%
on a water basis, but on an air basis, it has also increased by 11%.
If we talk about the running share of the company, then
in this quarter the earnings of the company have
come to Rs 718 paise, whereas in the previous  It was
₹12 two paise in the quarter and
in the December 2021 quarter of last year, the company's
earning purchase was ₹647, here also the
net profit is 40% declared, on the company's
earning on a quarterly basis in the share and if we
talk on year to year, then it has increased by 11%,
so overall if we
look at all the numbers of the company, then on a quarterly
basis, all the parameters of the company have
declined, but on an on-year basis, there has been
growth in it,
Islam, let's talk about the current share price of the company, then the
share price of the company as of today's date
is Rs 1249 crore, sorry,
1249 per share and if we look here, then according to this share
price, the company is more valuable on today's date, we will
tell you its reason, if we
talk about the price by book value of the company, then
today's price of this company is its
book ratio, the book value is
6.70, whereas if we talk about the book value in the price of the sector, then it is
2.34, that is
This stock is trading at a P/B of almost three times the sector's P/B. If we
talk about the stock
's price to earnings ratio, then the
P/B of the stock is 48, whereas the sector's price is
23, so according to that also it is double
bad. If we are checking the company on both the parameters, then
according to both the parameters, the company is valid,
because if the company is bad then there is
no benefit in investing because we will
buy it at a premium by paying extra price and by chance tomorrow the
company is not able to perform well, then the
price there will increase a lot, so
from an investment perspective, right now is
not the right time, but yes, if you have already
invested then take some profit, it keeps going, so if
you look at the quadrant on a basis, then on a year on
year basis, it is fine, the
profit of the company on this quadrant has decreased, so that's all
for today's results.
You must have liked the video, if you liked it,
like and share it.
Please do it and also subscribe to my channel,
thank you so much.